

ABOUT ME

Nationality: Indian

Date Of Birth: 01-10-1995

Marital Status: Married

Passport Number: S5039508

Visa Status: Visit Visa

EXPERTISE

- UI/UX Design
- Web Design
- Digital Marketing
- Graphic Design
- Web Development

LANGUAGE

- · English
- Hindi
- Malayalam
- Arabic (Beginner)

SKILLS

- Adobe Creative Suite
- UI/UX | App/ Web Design
- · Figma, Adobe XD
- HTML,CSS,Bootstrap,
- Javascript,jQuerry
- · React, vue, Node is, PHP
- Wordpress Elementor,
 Divi, WP Bakery
- Microsoft Office Excel, Word, Spreadsheet

CONTACT

(3) +971 58 200 2410

vikhi333@gmail.com

O Hor Al Anz, Deirah, Dubai

VIKHIL MUTHIYANGA

VISUAL DESIGNER & FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Hello! I'm Vikhil. I'm a BCA Graduate from Don Bosco Arts and Science College, Angadikadavu, Kannur, Kerala.

Im Self motivated person with positive attittude. I've been working as a Visual Designer for the past 5 years,

I can share my skills for Graphic, Web, UI/UX Design, Development and testing. I can manage small to large projects, also i can lead the junior designers and developers within a team.

EDUCATION

2011 - 2013

St.Mary's HSS, Edoor Biology Science | 79% Overall

2013 - 2016

Don Bosco Arts & Science College, Angadikkadavu

Bachelor of Computer Applications 53% | 2.13 CGPA

2021 - 2022

Spotix | Intern

Full Stack Development - MERN

3 month internship on Full Stack Development

WORK EXPERIENCE

2020 - 2023

Visual Designer - UI/UX Bridcodes Global

- Mobile / Web User interface Design
- Standardized all output with a new, responsive, mobile-first approach and strategy.
- logo, brochures social media collaterals
- Branding, Promotions, Campaigns for the business

2018 - 2020

2016 - 2018

Graphic , Web Designer
d'katia Software Technologies Pvt.Ltd, Kochi

- Created logos, advertising graphics, and websites for small businesses.
- Communicated with clients to understand their business goals and company cultures.
- Implemented websites and landing pages
- Standardized all output with a new, responsive, mobilefirst approach and strategy.
- Elementor, Divi, Wp bakery, wordpress development and security

Transaction Processor Conduent Business Solutions India Pvt. Ltd

- US Based Health Care Process Management
- · Analyse Data and Store it into database
- Support Clients through chats
- · Health Care Claim Handling and Processing
- Analyse Visual, test and transform it into a structured data.